{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Enterprise Architecture",
    "Term": "Finals",
    "Title": "Full Course Review",
    "LastModified": "16 December 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Finals Reviewer"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This component of TOGAF provides the \"way of working\" for architects.",
      "answer": "Architecture Development Method",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does CMMI stand for?",
      "answer": "Capability Maturity Model Integration",
      "choices": [
        "Capability Maturity Model Integration",
        "Capability Minority Model Integration",
        "Capability Maturity Model Incorporation",
        "Capability Maturity Model Intellegent"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This is considered as the blueprint of an enterprise that provides a common organizational understanding",
      "answer": "Business architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Business architecture",
        "Quality Management",
        "Strategic Management",
        "Business Model Development"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In MDA, this includes the business requirements and domain model that describes the state of the enterprise where the system will be integrated.",
      "answer": "Computation independent model",
      "choices": [
        "Computation independent model",
        "XML Metadata Interchange",
        "Platform-Independent Model",
        "Platform-Specific Model"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This pertains to a component of TOGAF that addresses the organization and processes required to establish and operate an architecture within an enterprise",
      "answer": "Architecture Capability Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This process involves the identification of the products and services that the business will sell, the target market, and the anticipated expenses.",
      "answer": "Business Model Development",
      "choices": [
        "Business Model Development",
        "Business Architecture",
        "Quality Management",
        "Strategic Management"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does TOGAF stand for?",
      "answer": "The Open Group Architecture Framework",
      "choices": [
        "The Open Group Architecture Framework",
        "Object Management Group",
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Control Objectives for Information and Related Technology"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a framework in which different issues can be easily mapped to understand its nature, implications, and possible solutions.",
      "answer": "Zachman Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Zachman Framework",
        "TOGAF",
        "CMMI",
        "ITIL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ITIL stand for?",
      "answer": "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
      "choices": [
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Information Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technology Infrastructure Library"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to a collection of organizations that has a common set of goals, objectives, and/or a single targeted outcome",
      "answer": "Enterprise",
      "choices": [
        "Enterprise",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Architecture",
        "Enterprise Architecture"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This is considered as the key feature of MDA",
      "answer": "Mapping",
      "choices": [
        "Mapping",
        "Sampling",
        "Driving",
        "Cooking"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It originated as a generic framework and methodology for developing technical architectures.",
      "answer": "TOGAF",
      "choices": [
        "TOGAF",
        "Zachman Framework",
        "CMMI",
        "ITIL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the Zachman framework formerly called?",
      "answer": "Framework for Information Systems Architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Framework for Information Systems Architecture",
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Framework for International Systems Architecture"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In CMMI, this phase involves processes that are planned, performed, and measured",
      "answer": "Managed",
      "choices": [
        "Managed",
        "Defined",
        "Initial",
        "Optimizing"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This TOGAF component specifically contains the business, data, application, and information technology architecture.",
      "answer": "Architecture Content Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The Open Groupâ€™s Standards Information Base (SIB) and the Building Blocks Information Base are reference models in the model-driven architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Platform-independent model (PIM) is one of the five (5) abstraction levels in model-driven architecture",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Data and application architecture are under the enterprise consortium of TOGAF.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The information technology (IT) architecture is one of the main components of the Zachman Framework.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>TOGAF was previously called \"Framework for Information Systems Architecture.\"",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Model-driven architecture has five (5) abstraction levels.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Architecture capability framework provides the \"way of working\" for architects in enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Computation independent model (CIM) includes the business requirements and business model or domain model, which describe the state of the enterprise where the system will be integrated.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Platform-specific model (PSM) combines the specifications in the PIM and the details on how a system uses a particular type of platform in the Zachman Framework.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Migration planning is included in the TOGAF stepwise cycle approach.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>TOGAF has a unique stepwise cycle approach when it comes to the method of architecture development.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Meta-object facility (MOF) provides a standard repository of the MDA model in enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Common warehouse meta-model (CWM) specifies interfaces that can be used in enabling easy interchange of data and business intelligence metadata between repositories, warehouse tools, and platforms in the TOGAF.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The four (4) main components of TOGAF architecture are capability framework, architecture development method, architecture content framework, and model-driven architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The Zachman Framework was recognized as the first comprehensive framework for enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It invovles the dissemination of information to all stakeholders.",
      "answer": "Informing",
      "choices": [
        "Informing",
        "Validation",
        "Obtaining commitment",
        "Maintaining the model"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling action can be done by adding specific details to existing elements.",
      "answer": "Refinement",
      "choices": [
        "Refinement",
        "Introduction",
        "Abstraction",
        "Translation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which statement best describes knowledge transformation?",
      "answer": "It is a situation where knowledge processes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a situation where knowledge processes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
        "It involves the condition and commitment of stakeholders on enterprise architecture.",
        "It depicts an enterprise architecture model in a specific manner based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process",
        "It is the primary and essential models that are used in the transformation of knowledge."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a VALID statement about limiting the visual complexity of a model?",
      "answer": "Reduce the number of relations depicted in a model.",
      "choices": [
        "Reduce the number of relations depicted in a model.",
        "Reduce the complexity of the concepts.",
        "Reduce the enemies to pieces.",
        "Reduce the number of submodels inside the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a metaphorical direction that goes towards the internal composition of an element.",
      "answer": "Inwards",
      "choices": [
        "Inwards",
        "Upwards",
        "Sidewards",
        "Downwards"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to perceive a line as uninterruptedly establishing a direction based on their perspective. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Continuity",
      "choices": [
        "Continuity",
        "Proximity",
        "Closure",
        "Similarity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These pertain to the primary and essential models that are used in the transformation of knowledge in enterprise architecture modeling.",
      "answer": "Central Representations",
      "choices": [
        "Central Representations",
        "Knowledge Representations",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Central Transformation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This activity requires checking whether the key stakeholders agree that the viewpoints in the model are correct.",
      "answer": "Validation",
      "choices": [
        "Validation",
        "Obtaining commitment",
        "Maintaining the model",
        "Informing"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In relation to modeling activities, which of the following refers to establishing the purpose, scope, and focus of a model?",
      "answer": "It is a goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the purpose of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the purpose of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
        "It serves as a guide in determining appropriate information to be included in the model.",
        "It involves requirements gathering, such as appropriate information, to create, structure, and visualize an enterprise architecture model.",
        "It uses the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate whether the model and the visualization achieved the intended outcome."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to documentation as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
      "choices": [
        "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context.",
        "Classify the newly introduced candidate element based on the concepts used in the model.",
        "Placing a fresh term for a concept or relation in the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to perceive comparable objects as though they belong together as a unit. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Similarity",
      "choices": [
        "Similarity",
        "Proximity",
        "Closure",
        "Continuity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to relate objects that are near to each other. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Proximity",
      "choices": [
        "Proximity",
        "Similarity",
        "Closure",
        "Continuity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling action involves the administration and documentation of other modeling actions.",
      "answer": "Documentation",
      "choices": [
        "Documentation",
        "Translation",
        "Abandoing",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Abandoning a modeling language",
      "choices": [
        "Abandoning a modeling language",
        "Documentation",
        "Abandoning a concept",
        "Refinement"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to refinement as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Classifying newly introduced candidate elements based on the modeling concept",
      "choices": [
        "Classifying newly introduced candidate elements based on the modeling concept",
        "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context.",
        "Placing a fresh term for a concept or relation in the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This pertains to the form in which a model is presented.",
      "answer": "Visualization",
      "choices": [
        "Visualization",
        "Model",
        "Representation",
        "Presentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This depicts an enterprise architecture model based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process.",
      "answer": "Knowledge Representation",
      "choices": [
        "Knowledge Representation",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Central Transformation",
        "Central Representations"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the act of placing a fresh term for a concept or relation within a model.",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Refinement",
        "Abandoning",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to abandoning as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Eliminating an element with proper documentation",
      "choices": [
        "Eliminating an element with proper documentation",
        "Can be done by adding specific details to existing elements.",
        "An architect decides whether information that is available in the model, is to be left out or not.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element.",
      "answer": "Translation",
      "choices": [
        "Translation",
        "Documentation",
        "Refinement",
        "Introduction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Gestalt Theory of Human Perception, which of the following scenarios pertain to common fate?",
      "answer": "People have the tendency to perceive different objects, which function in a similar manner, as a unit",
      "choices": [
        "People have the tendency to perceive different objects, which function in a similar manner, as a unit",
        "People have the tendency to perceive objects that are similar to belong together in a unit.",
        "Also known as 'tadhana'",
        "People have the tendency to perceive a line as continuous establishing directions based on their perspective."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "If modeling is considered a transformation process in enterprise architecture, which of the following statements is correct?",
      "answer": "Models can be used to describe the future situation of an organization",
      "choices": [
        "Models can be used to describe the future situation of an organization",
        "Goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the different purposes of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
        "Involves requirements gathering, such as appropriate information, to create, structure, and visualize an enterprise architecture model.",
        "Models are created using different viewpoints that give a specific set of concepts and relations to be used during the modeling process."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is NOT a valid statement regarding modeling actions?",
      "answer": "Documentation is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element",
      "choices": [
        "Documentation is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element",
        "Stakeholders and their needs must be considered in visualizing a model.",
        "Uses the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate whether the model and the visualization achieved the intended outcome.",
        "Models are created using different viewpoints that give a specific set of concepts and relations to be used during the modeling process."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Based on the modeling guidelines in enterprise architecture, which of the following is correct?",
      "answer": "Collect feedback from various stakeholders",
      "choices": [
        "Collect feedback from various stakeholders",
        "Use abstractions as frequent as possible.",
        "Introduce novel concepts and structures.",
        "Make the model such as it relies on additional explanation."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Gestalt Theory of Human Perception, which of the following scenarios pertains to closure?",
      "answer": "People have the tendency to perceive incomplete objects as complete",
      "choices": [
        "People have the tendency to perceive incomplete objects as complete",
        "People have the tendency to perceive objects that are similar to belong together in a unit.",
        "People have the tendency to perceive a line as continuous establishing directions based on their perspective.",
        "It's all in the past, pangga. Let's move on with our lives and let go of the past."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Relative to the representation conventions, which of the following best describes the use of layouts?",
      "answer": "This includes basic patterns, alignment, and object distribution",
      "choices": [
        "This includes basic patterns, alignment, and object distribution",
        "Shapes of objects in a model usually match the intrinsic properties of the real-life objects.",
        "Can also increase the appeal of a diagram but can also lead to contrary effects, such as confusion and distraction.",
        "Speeds up the creating of a proper mental state in modeling, while creating a good starting for the line of reasoning."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "If modeling is considered a transformation process in enterprise architecture, which of the following statement is INCORRECT?",
      "answer": "Enterprise architecture provides a high-level overview of an organization",
      "choices": [
        "Enterprise architecture provides a high-level overview of an organization",
        "Depicts an enterprise architecture model in a specific manner based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process.",
        "Knowledge passes through the modeling process while considering goals and guidelines.",
        "Goals under the modeling process of an enterprise architecture."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling activity utilize the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate the model.",
      "answer": "Using the model",
      "choices": [
        "Using the model",
        "Visualizing the model",
        "Creating and structuring the model",
        "Establishing the purpose, scope, and focus"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers to a situation where knowledge passes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
      "answer": "Knowledge transformation",
      "choices": [
        "Knowledge transformation",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Knowledge Representation",
        "Knowledge State"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is INCORRECT about modeling activities?",
      "answer": "Using a model requires validation",
      "choices": [
        "Using a model requires validation",
        "Requirements gathering is performed in model visualization.",
        "Enterprise architecture involves the identification of relationships between different domains while providing a high-level overview.",
        "Models can also be used to describe the current and future situation of an organization, as well as the possible development requirements."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling action can be done by adding specific details to existing elements",
      "answer": "Refinement",
      "choices": [
        "Refinement",
        "Risk analysis",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Use of colors"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Example of these are regulatory framework and government laws",
      "answer": "External Driver",
      "choices": [
        "External Driver",
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Private business process",
        "Application usage viewpoint"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This viewpoint depicts the relationships of applications in a company, including the dependencies in terms of the services a company offers",
      "answer": "Application association viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This process helps architects to identify and manage potential problems that could arise within the project period",
      "answer": "Risk analysis",
      "choices": [
        "Risk analysis",
        "Refinement",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Selecting viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This type of business process modeling notation element includes sub-processes, loops, and compensation",
      "answer": "Activity",
      "choices": [
        "Activity",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Private business process",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a visual attribute that is strongly influenced by \"prior knowledge\"",
      "answer": "Use of colors",
      "choices": [
        "Use of colors",
        "External Driver",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Application usage viewpoint"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It contains equipment such as machines, tools, and/or instruments that can create, use, store, move, or transform materials",
      "answer": "Physical viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Selecting viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It pertains to a viewpoint that describes how applications are used to support one (1) or more business processes",
      "answer": "Application usage viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "External Driver"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a sub-model within a business process modeling notation diagram that involves internal processes to a specific organization and does not cross organizational boundaries",
      "answer": "Private business process",
      "choices": [
        "Private business process",
        "Activity",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a structural unified modeling language diagram that depicts the physical resources in a system, including nodes, components, and connections",
      "answer": "Deployment diagram",
      "choices": [
        "Deployment diagram",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Refinement"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It aims to provide an open and vendor-neutral approach to interoperability and raises the level of abstraction in enterprise architecture",
      "answer": "Model-Driven Architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Selecting viewpoints",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Examples of these are the mission and vision of an organization",
      "answer": "Internal Drivers",
      "choices": [
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It provides high-level insight into the general operations of the company, which is used to structure an organization according to its main activities",
      "answer": "Business function viewpoints",
      "choices": [
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This serves as a guide in determining appropriate information to be included in a model",
      "answer": "Selecting viewpoints",
      "choices": [
        "Selecting viewpoints",
        "Refinement",
        "Activity",
        "Business function viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    }
  ]
}